Oh, the light of my eyes...
The fire of my heart...
Is she alive?
Alaca.
Alaca. Is she..
Bala who cures with her hands
and heals with her heart is alive?
You feel too, right?
You fell Bala too.
That's why you've come up here.
Is that why you showed me the way?
Hey, is she alive? You can't
contain yourself either, right?
If only you knew the storms
breaking up in my heart.
If only you knew Alaca.
You felt her. That's why you have come here.
My Bala..
You're alive.
You are alive...
You've sent Alaca to me.
Oh my dear...
Let's go.
Come on.
There must be some trails around here.
There must be some trails around
here. Some trails around here.
Around here..
Oh these trails...
Trails..
They captured Bala.
They imprisoned her.
Oh no...
These trails...
Trails..
Halime.
Was that why you appeared
in my dreams, my daughter?
My Halime's talisman.
Halime, is that you?
Are you here, my daughter?
My Halime.
Is that you my dear?
Are you here my dear?
Wait.
Don't go.
I couldn't realize.
I couldn't realize the reason
of those dreams, my dear.
My Osman..
Our daughter is alive, Osman.
Our precious is alive.
Thank God, I raised her. What if you did?
It would be a pity.
Sofia.
Where is my daughter?
Where is my Halime, Sofia?
Sofia, don't go. Don't go!
Don't run away! Where is my daughter?
Where is my Halime? She is my daughter Sofia!
Where is my daughter? Sofia!
Sofia!
Demon!
What are you doing here?
-Is what I heard true?
-What did you hear?
Don't you lie to me! I heard everything!
Osman and Bala's daughter... Is Halime alive?
What did you mean?
You said you took away her daughter.
You said you raised her.
You said...
You said she remembers nothing.
Did you...
Let's go to your room. Not here.
Let's go.
Meals shall be cooked! Tables shall be set!
Celebrate our glorious victory!
Osman..
He ran away without looking behind.
In the woods,
...he defeated us with his mind.
Yet we keep the heart of the state.
We are the winner.
Yet Osman is still alive.
-That means hope for his people.
-He's going to die!
Ilbay, he's going to die.
Nobody has ever got rid of Ulugan's clutches.
Neither will Osman.
I will...
..take the hope out of people's hearts.
He's going to die for sure.
With Bala, we already
took out the half of his heart.
Yet I'm curious.
Sofia was with us when we
went to look for Bala Hatun.
But she hasn't been around.
She wasn't leading her army either.
Where was Sofia when Osman attacked?
What are you chewing in your mouth, woman?
Just spill the beans.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that red demon can do anything.
We should hold her leash tightly.
I'm quite sure that she's up to something.
I don't give an ear to a woman's words.
But at times..
...you say right things.
Altuga.
Prepare the horses.
-We're going to Akhisar.
-Ulugan.
Tracks. Tracks..
Tracks...
Tracks!
The tracks disappear here.
Where did they take her?
My Allah... Where did they take her? No... No...
No...
Is someone playing a game, huh?
Is someone playing a game with me?
No... no..
No! No!
I will not lose hope.
I will not give up hope.
No. Right? Right, Alaca?
Right? Otherwise, you wouldn't have
brought me all the way here. Right, Alaca?
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
made me search for Bala like this.
No.
With the help of my Allah, we will do this.
In my heart..
Right here in my heart...
I feel she is still alive.
With my Allah's help...
...we will find Bala.
We will. Surely we will.
We will find her.
Who did this? Who did this?
-Begum Hatun, my Bey...
He is right.
Begum Hatun made this treacherous move.
She got on her horse and went this way.
Begum..
What tricks are you playing, huh?
I will find you, and then you
will see what I will do to you.
You will see what I will do to you.
Tell me something! What I heard is confusing me.
What is confusing you. Poena? Tell me!
Is Halime really alive?
If you raised her then I...
Unless..
Unless Halime is me..
-Poena!
Have you become stupid since
you started living with them?
Or have you forgotten who I am?
What are you trying to say?
Poena.
Halime is dead.
While they are alive, I want Bala and Osman...
...to feel the same pain we
have felt. Do you understand me?
So did you lie to them?
Of course, I lied.
If I had done such a thing,
wouldn't I have told you?
I thought that...
Come. Come, my little bird come.
Sit down.
Poena.
Don't let meaningless
thoughts confuse your mind.
What you have been through is not easy.
Besides...
...at such a young age, you
are carrying such a big revenge.
It is normal for you to be tired now.
Drink.
Look, Poena...
Thanks to this lie...
...Osman and Bala will suffer the
grief of losing a child once again.
We will make them pay heavily...
...for the pain they caused you.
Do not forget to take your medicine again.
Drink some more.
Alright. What will happen now, aunt?
Do not worry about this now.
Have some rest. Come on, drink it. Drink it.
When you wake up...
..your pain will be gone.
Halime.
I will not kill you before
making you talk, Sofia.
You will take me to my Halime.
I have to get out of here.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Osman Bey is coming!
Welcome, my Bey.
Father..
Are you alright?
You left without saying
anything after the raid on the tribe.
I am alright, my daughter. Don't worry.
I am alright.
Tell me.
What is the situation?
While we were burying our martyr, Saruca Bey...
We received your order then, my Bey.
We immediately withdrew from Sogut to here.
Shamil and Turhan are leading
one troop of watchmen and
Aykurt and Kanyumaz are
leading the other group, my Bey.
Our precautions are complete.
The enemies..
...are after me and my family.
Staying in Sogut would be more
dangerous for our innocent people.
That's why we will stay here secretly
for a while until we take our tribe.
But no one will reveal themselves or the tribe.
Father...
We were...
...going to bury my mother in the tribe.
But now...
We will, my daughter.
We will.
What is happening to you?
Why do you bow your heads?
Why do you surrender to sorrow? Don't!
Uluga
That dog Ulugan learned about our plan.
We had to return. But do not forget.
We did not give up, we did not fall.
Even if I die, I will never
step back from my oath.
That's why, when the time comes...
...we will take our tribe.
We will take our land.
-God willing. God willing my Bey.
But we have never given up
on our oath as well my Bey.
If necessary, we will give our lives.
But we will never give up on your path.
Your oath is our oath, my
Bey. We will take our tribe.
We will bury my mother
next to my sister, God willing.
God willing.
God willing. God willing.
Follow me.
Soldiers!
Welcome Ulugan.
You haven't been seen around lately.
You send me soldiers...
...but do not lead the army.
You go into your den like a fox...
...and stay silent.
And you see yourself above me...
...and do not stand up.
What is your problem, Sofia?
I do not see myself above you, Ulugan.
But you should not see yourself above me either.
Lukas died.
All his power and strength are now mine.
No, mine.
What you call "your property" is only mine.
I gave you the castles Osman took from you.
Where is my gold?
Unlike you, we respect our dead.
When Lukas died, I took care of him.
I will give you your gold.
Of course, you will.
You would not stay behind these cold walls...
...for nothing, Sofia.
While Osman walks freely
outside, you would not hold back.
What are you hiding from me. Red Hatun?
Nothing.
I am just mourning.
Wake up!
You need to eat enough to stay alive.
Master Sofia still has a lot to do
with you. I am talking to you, get up!
Open the door, something is happening.
Hold this.
What is happening? What
is happening? Call a doctor!
Die!
Wait for me, Sofia.
I'm coming.
We all know the situation.
While capturing Sogut and taking the tribe back.
...we lost too many alps.
We lost strength.
But now we should...
...turn the situation into a weapon against
which heathens will get caught unaware.
How will we do that, my Bey?
I mean... What's in your mind?
They think we have fallen weak.
Nobody expects us to attack.
But we will make them know...
...Turks never stop fighting
though their wings are broken.
Let them keep looking for us.
We will..
...raid the biggest Turkmen
tribe under Mongolian authority.
So we will also break Ulugan's
noker(Mongolian soldier) force.
Absolutely.
First, we need to free the people in captivity.
Then we'll take Turkmen
Beys and their alps on our side.
Now it's the best time to gain
power. You're right, my Bey.
My sons.
You two have this duty.
Boran, Cerkutay and Yusuf...
You and I will have another task.
Come on, sons. Get prepared and leave quickly.
Well, my Bey...
What is our task?
Listen to me carefully now.
I'm coming, Sofia. I'm coming.
Soldiers! Escort Ulugan.
Sofia..
Hristo, make sure that Ulugan has left quietly.
He shouldn't know about Bala.
Bala!
Sofia!
Where is my daughter, Sofia?
Soldiers!
Shut up!
You've sent all the soldiers with Ulugan.
You can't beat us even if
all of you get united, Sofia!
You will never behave, right?
You did such a thing to me...
...that the fire inside me will never
die even if you kill me a thousand times!
-Take me to my daughter.
-Never.
I will never do that.
I'll kill you, Sofia.
I will kill you!
You can't do anything, Bala.
If you kill me, you can't find Halime.
Only I know where she is.
I know she's alive.
I'll certainly find my daughter.
But if you don't want to die
you have to take me to her
Get up
Get up! Move!
You'll take me to my daughter, Sofia. Move!
I'll kill you after I find my daughter. Move!
Look at this.
Who is here?
Ulugan.
I thought you were dead, hatun.
Even the fire didn't accept you, huh?
Death comes from Allah, Ulugan.
It seems I still have time to see your death.
Your weak head..
...would fall on the ground
with one move of my sword.
-Bala...
-But no.
You have to see your
impertinent husband's death first.
Nokers(Mongolian soldiers)!
You kept Bala from me, huh?
Begum made a stupid
decision and I made use of it.
I was going to tell you when it was time.
Soldiers, give her clothes to her
before taking her to the dungeon.
Bala..
He's not sharing his plan again.
We're going after a secret, brother.
I'm curious too, brother.
But Beys have secrets, you know.
So keep silent.
Look what you say!
Brother, why is he not trusting us?
What if he even tells us?
Would we say no? Never!
Wouldn't we trust him?
Wouldn't we join his cause?
How can I know, Cerkutay?
We may question if tells us.
Maybe that's why he's not telling.
You know what?
Without knowing the
secret, I will speak no more.
Speak, question or get
curious just for once! But no!
-Don't question your duty just for once.
-What are you talking about?
My Bey..
We have been wondering...
We're getting closer to the tribe, you know.
You didn't explain our duty.
Will we infiltrate the tribe, my Bey?
No.
One of tribe people is coming to meet us.
Your sister.
Send a message to the tribe with alps.
Getting a message from you,
she will definitely come here.
-She will have her punishment later.
-As you order, my Bey.
What? Why are you upset?
Those who made me upset
shall be ashamed, my Bey.
It shouldn't have been like this.
It's your right, though.
It's your true right to avenge Bala Hatun.
Don't be embarrassed. Ever.
You and your sister have different characters.
Well... One is born as a man.
The other is born as a dog.
Yes, my Bey. May Allah be pleased with you.
Don't worry.
I know how to bring her here.
Brother.
You're worried about father, right?
He was acting differently, brother.
He took only Boran Bey,
Cerkutay Bey and Yusuf with him.
They even told them nothing.
The fire Osman Bey will start has no limits now.
We'll find out when it is time.
Let's save those Turkmen villages...
...from the Mongolians dogs first.
Yes, yes.
If they notice us.
...they'll kill women and children first.
We won't let them notice.
We'll take care of the nokers(Mongolian soldiers)
at the gate first.
Then...
...we will jump on them when they never expect!
Samil, Aykurt.
Go ahead and check the situation.
As you order, my Shahzade.
We'll find out their plans.
Alright.
For every life they took,
...we will be hell for them.
Whatever you do, I won't stop.
You'll never be able to
get out of this place, Bala.
Ever.
You'll see, Sofia.
I won't stop until I take
back what you took from me.
Stop dreaming, Bala.
Look at this place!
This will be a grave for Osman and you!
Sofia.
Sofia!
Sofia
You lied to me, girl.
Next time
..I will kill you.
Killing me wouldn't be good for you, Ulugan.
Our enemy is Osman.
And we both want him to die.
I just...
...want him to die suffering.
If you play with the prey,
...you lose the prey.
If you waste time
..you lose it.
I never lose, Ulugan.
I took his heart out.
I won't die before I kill you, Sofia.
I won't die before I kill you!
Send the good news to Osman.
The Hatun is alive.
He can know now.
Osman..
...will come running to his death, Bala.
Your great love...
...will be Osman's death
Sofia! Sofia come here! Sofia, no!
Osman... Osman
Sofia! Osman! Osman, no!
Yusuf...
Brother..
Kayis tried to take their
anger on you through me.
I don't know how long I
can live with this wound.
I am hiding in Saripinar.
Even though you have been on
the wrong way, you are my sister.
Yusuf.
Before I take my last breathy my
last wish is to ask for your pardon.
If you come quickly, you
can find me before I die.
If not, it's alright.
Protect our father's ring.
My pardon is yours.
Your brother, Yusuf.
Yusuf...
Brother..
Not only this ring, you are
also a trust from my father to me.
It s because of me.
won t..
...let this happen.
Begum, what are you doing?
Osman is looking for you
everywhere! Where are you going?
I am going to Yusuf! They tried to
kill him! I'll go and see him! Move!
What if it's Yusuf's plan? Didn't
your brother betray us before?
He betrayed you.
He betrayed Ulugan. Not me.
He wouldn't harm me. I said move.
No, Begum. No. You're not thinking clearly now.
If necessary. I'll protect you better than you
can protect yourself. You can't go anywhere.
-Ilbay, get out of my way.
-You can't go anywhere. -Move! -No, Begum!
Let go.
So you are the key to find Bala, Begum, huh?
Now you will pay for your evilness.
You will tell me everything one by one.
My Bey, this traitor will not
come. I say we sneak into the tribe.
Let's catch this traitor and give
her her punishment. And it'll be over!
He says he'll sneak into the tribe. Oh, well.
Brother, take it slow when sneaking in.
Remember what happened the last
time you tried to sneak in. We all know.
And that place is no longer
our tribe, it's a den of jackals.
It's hard to enter, even
harder to leave, Cerkutay.
Not our tribe, huh?
Did you say those things to me?
When a smart one is looking for a bridge...
..a fool crosses the water.
What did I do? I didn't sit and
wait like you. I crossed the water!
You are insane.
She will come, my Bey. Don't worry.
When she sees my father's ring,
she'll come to see me for the last time.
God willing.
God willing she will come.
To your positions.
How did Bala run away? Are you alright?
I am alright, my little bird.
Today is the big day.
How are you feeling?
The big day?
It is time to take your revenge, Poena.
Today, Osman and Bala are going to die.
You are going to take your
mother's and father's revenge.
You will tell Osman...
...Bala is alive. -How?
Am I going to tell him?
Why would he believe me?
-He is going to believe you.
And since you'll be the one saying
it, he won't suspect that it's a trap.
He'll ask how I know.
I thought of everything.
Now..
...listen to me carefully.
Yusuf!
Yusuf, brother! -Sister!
I am here, get off the horse!
Yusuf, come here, brother!
Show yourself!
You..
...are not injured.
Traitor Begum.
Finally, you are before us.
Now, for the things you did
to my Hatun, to my Bala...
Now you will pay for what you did.
You lured me into a trap although
you knew they'd kill me, Yusuf!
I told you.
I told you not to do this!
You did not listen to me!
Shame on the efforts I put into you.
You deserved to die from the beginning, sister.
You cannot run away.
You will give me answers for the things you did!
Come on.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Come on! Move!
Life was given to your miserable souls...
...for serving the Mongols.
If you don't work, there is no food, only death.
The Righteous!
We will be the nightmare of
those who try to capture the Turks!
Kayis!
Osman's dog!
Those we killed in the tribe didn't
make you give up, huh? Nokers!
Attack! -Attack, brothers!
We will take the women and children
to the back of the tents. Let's go!
We'll move them away from the battle, come on!
Allah is the Greatest!
Osman's dog...
I will tear apart that courage of yours.
I will place your head under my feet.
The sparks of courage
burning like a blazing fire in the
heart of a Turk, have been
passed down from eternity.
And they will continue
burning forever, for sure.
You've come to your death,
but you are still smiling.
What kind of a person are you?
It's not me, you are the
ones going to death. Nokers(Mongolian soldiers)!
You were right Ilbay Bey.
Even siblings can betray each other.
If the devil was here, even he
would be ashamed of what you did.
But don't worry.
I will be your executioner.
Did you think I would
fall for your trick, Osman?
Now, I have the power. Your
punishment is death. Nokers! Attack!
Come at me then!
I know the games you've played. Where is Bala?
You've lost your mind, Osman.
Bala is in hell. I burned her alive.
You brought my sister into
this, Ilbay. You are the reason!
Your sister is on the right path. You
are the one who is on the wrong way.
Join us, Yusuf.
I would die but never leave my Osman Bey.
I know Bala is alive. You did this to
lure me into a trap. Where is Bala?
Bala's pain made you lose your mind.
You are not sane anymore. I said I
burned her, why don't you understand?
My Bey, there are more of these dogs.
Alps, follow me.
Everyone will see.
Whoever is the enemy of the Turks
will find no peace in both worlds.
Come here, my dear. Come, my child.
Don't be afraid, my dear.
Don't be afraid, my child.
Go to the back of the tent.
Don't be afraid, my dear.
Sahin Bey!
Sahin Bey, are you alright?
Are you alright?
Osman Bey...
Osman Bey never leaves
someone in captivity, Sahin Bey.
Sure, Alaeddin Bey!
Come on! Take this sword! Come on!
Ulugan will make you pay for this raid!
Your alps and people will die!
Are you trying to fear the one who
is asking for shahada with death?
Turks are not scared of
anything, except for captivity!
Now... Now I will send you to hell.
But don't worry. Your owner will come soon.
Are you alright Sahin Bey?
Thanks to Allah.
Captivity is over.
Now
...I want revenge, Orhan Bey.
Okay.
That's why we are here.
Okay. Sahin Bey...
Osman Bey knows that every Turk
seeks a solution for the Mongol trouble.
But the solution... "the
solution is obvious" he says.
Osman Bey wants to...
...unite and attack these dastards.
Sahin Bey...
...there will be many axes
waiting to attack a lonely tree.
We say..
...let's be a mighty forest.
What do you say, what is your decision?
We will defend Osman Bey's da'wah with my
valiants until the last drop of our blood...
...and we will be on his side.
Thank you.
Thank you, Sahin Bey.
Once the blessed lineage of Oghuz unites,
even the steepest mountains will become flat.
Now, with this unity, we will destroy
the enemy against us, for sure.
For sure.
-Live long.
-Thank you.
How did we fall into this trap, my Bey?
Why didn't we kill Begum when we first saw her?
If you had allowed me, I
would have shot my arrow
struck her in the heart,
and she would have died.
Do you think I didn't think of these things?
Do you think I didn't consider the traps...
...Ilbay would set for us? Or
the treachery Begum planned?
Forgive me, my Bey, but then
why did we make this plan?
My intention...
...is not just Begum's death.
What is your intention, my Bey?
There's one thing I believe.
Bala.
Bala Hatun might be alive.
What are you saying, my Bey?
My Bey...
I don't want to repeat it but...
But, Bala Hatun burned before our eyes.
Who is that?
Meryem. What are you doing here?
I was looking for you everywhere, my Bey.
I need to give you important news.
What is this important matter?
Bala Hatun is alive, my Bey.
How?
How come?
Girl, are you hearing yourself?
You heard right, my Bey.
Bala Hatun is alive.
-Bala...
What's happening, my Allah?
What kind of test is this?
How is that possible?
Tell me everything from the beginning.
I had lost my dagger which was
a keepsake from my grandmother.
Thinking I must have dropped in
the cabin, I checked and found it there.
Meryem, where did you see Bala Hatun?
I didn't see Bala Hatun. But...
I got lost sometime.
I saw Byzantine soldiers and hid somewhere.
Then I heard them talking. They
said Bala Hatun was alive, my Bey.
My Allah...Thank You. Thank You.
Girl, tell me. Where are they keeping her?
Akhasir... They talked about
a place something like that.
-Akhisar?
-Yes, my Bey. Akhisar.
-They're keeping her there.
-Akhisar, huh?
Akhisar.
If it is Akhisar,
...this is Sofia's doing.
Get on the horses now! Come on!
Near Akhisar
We'll go inside silently.
We'll save Bala and destroy their place.
You go that way.
Cerkutay, you go that way.
As you order, my Bey.
Here we go.
Turks will be just history.
And their freaky tribe smelling
like goats will be a stable!
-That's Osman.
-Yes, Osman.
History can't be written without Turks.
But you people will be wiped out.
Open it.
We need to get out of here before the dawn.
I've dreamed of this for years.
Finally,
...you're really going to die before my eyes.
And the souls of my parents...
...will find peace.
You're a dangerous woman, Sofia.
I get that
If you keep one more thing from me.
If you ignore me and do things on your own
...your pretty face will be wasted, Sofia.
Did you hear me well?
Whatever you are for Mongolians
...I'm the same thing for Byzantine, Ulugan.
I won't do anything against you.
But don't confuse me with the dogs...
...under your command.
Tell me.
How will you make Osman come here?
-What if he doesn't come? -He will.
Because it wasn't me who
told him that Bala is here.
Do you rely on your spy among them?
Not the spy.
I sent Osman a proof.
He has so many stupid men around him...
...that they didn't realize it was from me.
Then...
Pray for your God, Sofia.
Pray that it will happen...
...and Osman will fall into my clutches.
He already did, Ulugan.
He'll be here soon.
Be quiet.
Easy, easy.
-Here is the door leading to the dungeons.
-Stop!
-Who are you?
-Who are they?
There will be noise, my Bey.
My Bey, you go to the dungeons.
More dogs will come. We can hold the door.
Alright.
Come here, you rabid dogs!
We'll paint the walls of
Akhisar with your blood!
I will be your death.
I will bury you in these dungeons!
Osman. Osman
You vile dogs. Bala!
-Bala...
I'm here, Osman.
Come here.
Osman?
Osman!
Osman... Osman
Osman... Osman.
-Bala.
-You're here.
-I am.
-I will never leave you.
-No.
-You never will.
-I will never leave you.
Just wait. Thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Allah.
I'm here for you.
Bala.
You're really here.
What did they do to you?
-What did they do? Let me take off these.
-I'm fine.
You're here now. I'm better.
Take off these.
Take these off. Wait. Easy, easy.
Come on.
My Bala.
My beautiful-eyed woman.
I thought...
I thought you were... You were in the cabin.
I saw you in flames.
You know how much they made us suffer?
I thought you got burned.
But thanks to Allah, you are here now.
You're alive now. Are you alright?
I'm fine and alive.
-Thanks to Allah.
Thanks to Allah.
Let's go.
-Let's go.
-Osman, I need to tell you something.
Sofia told me such a thing...
-My Bey!
My Bey, my Bey!
Bala Hatun.
-Boran. Cerkutay.
-Bala Hatun.
Thanks to Allah, Bala Hatun.
God willing, you're fine.
Thanks to Allah, I'm good.
Let's go. We need to talk.
My lady.
It happened as you said. Osman came for Bala.
He's about to fall into our trap.
I told you, Ulugan.
It seems you sacrificed many soldiers for Osman.
You can't hunt without a bait.
I'll have avenged all of them
when Osman falls into our clutches.
Very soon.
Osman, listen to me. Sofia...
-Bala...
I have to get you
out of here alive first.
Osman!
Did you think you could
take your wife and run away?
You're coming after us like a
bunch of snakes again, huh?
I won't bury you only here
but deep in hell as well.
You're struggling in vain.
You've come into your own grave.
I see that you can hardly carry your head.
You're fighting with dirty tricks.
Are you not ashamed of this cowardice at all?
Attack!
Come here. Move.
-Sofia.
-Stop.
-Aunt.
You can't kill me, Osman.
Oh no?
Especially your wife
Bala won't let you do that.
Don't kill her, Osman.
Only she knows where our child is.
What are you saying, Bala?
Bala.
What are you saying?
My Bey.
Bala! Bala!
You heard right, Osman. Your daughter Halime...
..is alive.
She's right, Osman.
-How? How?
-Our daughter is alive.
We'll take our daughter
back, Osman. I can feel it.
Our child is alive!
-Hristo!
-Take Bala away.
-Bala!
Osman, we'll take her back.
-My Bey!
Get off!
Meryem, what are you doing here?
Poena.
Meryem.
What is Meryem doing here? Take Meryem out!
Let's go, my Bey.
We need to go.
We're outnumbered.
I won't leave Bala.
My Bey, they can't harm
her before they catch us.
-Boran is in there. Let's go, my Bey.
-Cerkutay.
-They're running off!
Attack!
Dastards! Osman is in there! Leave me!
-Leave me!
-Both you and Osman will die soon.
We'll see who is going to die.
Osman!
I'll take your heart out with my teeth.
After I save Bala, I will
butcher you and your people.
Attack!
Put it up!
Osman, hear me!
If you don't come to Sivrihoyuk tomorrow
and declare that you have surrendered.
...you will watch your wife die in that square!
Do you hear me?
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Hatuns and I made rose sherbet.
Thanks.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Do you like it?
It's delicious. Thank you.
Holofira Hatun.
Didn't you promise me that
you wouldn't tire yourself?
I didn't get tired. Don't worry.
Don't be upset, sister.
We are saying that as we care for you.
If Mother Bala were here
..she wouldn't let you do anything.
She wouldn't let you touch anything.
She wouldn't.
My mother isn't here anymore.
She's gone.
My sister.
My pretty-faced sister.
Fatma, our mother isn't dead.
Look. She is living here
She'll be here until we meet in the afterworld.
My pretty sister.
What mother and father liked most
was seeing you all together like this.
Yes, yes.
We will always be together like this.
We'll keep fighting for our
cause beside our father.
That's right.
We haven't got any news from Boran Bey, right?
Nobody has come to the tribe.
Our father must have a plan, Alaaddin.
He'd have told us if we needed to know.
We carried out the duty properly,
thank Allah.
If we don't get any news till the morning
...we will go after them, brother.
Alright, brother.
My Bey, before we entered the dungeon tunnels,
...those heathens noticed us.
Did we make a mistake or get
caught unaware? How did that happen?
My Bey, what if that red demon's words are true?
They're making use of our grief.
They're playing with our minds and hearts.
Then..
We should save Bala
Hatun before Sivrihoyuk, huh?
We will.
Of course, we will.
After Boran watches those
heathens and locates Bala,
...we will make a plan accordingly.
My Bey.
You're bleeding.
You got wounded while protecting me.
Let me bandage it.
Here, girl. Take this.
Take this.
Bandage it with this napkin as red as my blood.
Nothing else would cure me.
My Bey.
We should also cauterize it.
What happened to your great trick, Sofia?
Osman was just in our clutches.
But your foolish soldiers let him escape.
That was his last escape.
Yet he won't stop.
Bala.
She was talking about someone named Halime.
Who is she?
I told stupid Bala...
...that her dead daughter was alive.
So she will die a thousand
times before she actually dies.
She believed it.
You keep...
...playing games. Red Hatun.
But Osman..
...will come here with a bigger game.
He will try sneaking in again for sure.
But he will never be able to find her.
I will take Bala to my secret temple.
Osman doesn't even know such a place exists.
I will not tolerate a single mistake. Red Hatun.
I want Osman to die as soon as possible.
Osman and Bala will die in pain!
And this will happen thanks to me. Know that.
Soldiers, get ready.
We will secretly take her away.
Will they take Bala Hatun away?
Osman's spies might be around!
Everyone will be on alert!
No one will stop until we arrive in the temple!
They will take Bala Hatun to the temple.
Dastard dogs...
I have to go to my Bey!
Come on..
Bala. Bala.
Are you thinking about
Osman and worrying about him?
No.
I was thinking of how I would kill you
once I get rid of these chains, coward.
Once you get rid of these
chains, you'll die with Osman.
You are used to staying in
those small tents in your little tribe.
The air here hasn't been good for you.
That little mind of yours is clouded.
Soldiers! Prepare Bala Hatun!
Let's take her out for a little walk.
Where will you take me?
To the place where you will wake up
from your dreams and face the reality.
We are going to Sofia's secret temple.
We destroyed Sofia's temple.
Do not underestimate Master Sofia, Bala.
We are going to the secret temple.
No one knows where it is.
Good.
We will destroy that place as well then.
l am sorry, my Bey.
You are wounded because of me.
Being wounded is not important.
You are alright, that's what matters.
You saved my life for many times.
-No.
You treated my wounds. That's enough.
My Meryem daughter...
Why did you come after
us? You put your own life...
...and our lives at risk.
-I...
-You?
Cerkutay.
I felt guilty.
Bala Hatun..
...was abducted because I left to collect herbs.
And I couldn't do anything.
I came after you...
...to help you. -She is brave.
Brave, right.
Maybe that's why we love her.
Maybe that's why we...
..saw her as one of us.
Now...
...how are you going to save Bala
Hatun from that castle, my Bey?
My Bey...
Boran Bey is here.
-Boran!
-Peace be upon you.
Where are they keeping Bala? Is there any news?
Bala Hatun is not in the castle, my Bey.
They took her to a temple.
I wanted to go after them and follow them but...
...they were gone when I left the castle.
So fear has surrounded
the walls of the castle as well.
What else did you hear?
My Bey, Bala Hatun will stay at
the temple she was taken to tonight.
Then they will go to the square
where Ulugan called you, my Bey.
The most vicious dogs of this
Sofia snake will also be there.
In the other temple, they also
have as many men, my Bey.
-Yusuf.
-My Bey.
You will go to Orhan and Alaeddin. They...
...must have freed the
Alps held captive in the tribe.
Since we are entering the war, then...
...we need valiants, we need men.
-Yes my Bey.
Don't...
Don't tell Shahzades...
...that Bala Hatun is alive.
I will tell them everything.
-As you order.
My Allah..
Osman Bey Secret Tents
...forgive my mother' sins, my Allah...
May You make her a
neighbor to our dear Prophet.
My Bey...
May Allah accept it.
Thank you Hatun.
Thank you. -My Alaeddin...
Seeing the pain in your heart...
..and not being able to ease it hurts me.
My mother has been
my most difficult test.
After my Halime...
...I was always afraid.
Every night...
Every night, I slept with the fear that my
mother might not wake up in the morning.
Test..
People...
...are tested in this world with
the ones they love the most...
...and with the things they want the most...
Right...
We will get over this together again, my rose.
When time comes, we will
come together with my mother...
...my sister...
...and our daughter.
We will.
Come here.
What is this Gonca?
It belongs to Meryem.
I was going to give it to
Fatma, but I could not find her.
I'll keep it here for now...
...I will give it to her when I see her.
Meryem... has not returned yet, right?
I asked the Alps, Alaeddin.
But no one has seen her.
Let me put this somewhere.
My Bey, why didn't you tell the
Shahzades that Bala Hatun is alive?
I couldn't have told them without being sure.
I cannot stand seeing them upset
again after giving them the good news.
Bala Hatun is my matter.
But the state... There is
no emotion in the state.
Stability is essential in the state.
I sent Orhan and Alaeddin to Turkmen tribes.
I want everyone to see that our
struggle for existence continues.
Okay my Bey.
Whatever you do, you always do what's right.
Thank you.
Father..
She is having a dream, my Bey.
Let me give her some water.
No.
Don't.
Let her at least see her father in her dreams.
Fate has not shown her...
...either her mother or her father.
Let her.
-But she has a strong heart, my Bey.
-Yes.
Yes, she does.
There are not many like her at her age.
I brought you to your daughter, Bala.
My Halime..
My daughter...
Look..
Look at this place.
How does it feel?
Can you feel it?
They say mothers can feel it.
Your daughter grew up here.
She lived here for five years.
She stayed in all the temples with me.
She is different than you...
..and Osman.
She is like me, Bala.
She is a good Christian.
I will drown you in your own poison, Sofia.
Look.
This corner..
Right there...
She cried there for days.
She waited for her father,
she asked for her mother.
But you did not come, Bala.
Mother, father... where are you?
Halime.
Then..
...since you did not come...
...she held on to me.
She asked me to tell her tales.
What was it?
The little gazelle...
...in the forest...
Here.
Smell it.
I am not telling you a tale.
I am the truth itself.
Look..
It's her doll.
She always kept this with her.
Do not forget my favor, Bala.
Spend enough time with
her belongings before you die.
Sofia.
Sofia, where is my daughter?
Open the door!
Where is my daughter?
Where is my daughter, Sofia?!
She is not your daughter, Bala.
She is my daughter.
No! No! Sofia! No!
Open the door!
She is my daughter, Sofia!
Open the door! She is not yours!
Open the door!
Sofia!
She is my daughter...
Were you afraid, my daughter?
If I had known, wouldn't I have come, my dear?
Wouldn't your mother have come?
Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid, my daughter. Don't be afraid.
Don't be afraid, my daughter.
I am here.
I am here Halime.
My Bey, Shahzades are coming.
Let them come. Let them.
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you, my Bey.
Peace be upon you too, sons.
Finally you are here.
My Bey...
We raided the Turkmen tribe as you ordered.
We gained the support of their Beys
and gathered their Alps behind us.
Now, they wait for your order in the forest.
Thank you, sons, thank you.
Meryem.
What is Meryem doing here, my Bey?
Come on my daughter, you helped us enough.
I did not send you away
because it was dark outside. Now...
...now go to Fatma as soon as possible.
Yusuf. -My Bey.
They will take her there safely.
-As you order my Bey.
Come, sister.
Brother...
Children..
Come, sit.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
Father...
You have also warned Yusuf not to speak.
What are you doing here, my Bey?
We are close to Akhisar, my Bey.
Is your intention to gather the Turkmen
Alps behind us and surround the castle?
But no...
We are not strong enough for now.
Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun is alive.
What?
Father?
My mother is alive, huh?
My Bey, what are you saying -Children...
She is alive.
My Bey, what are you saying? -She is alive.
My Allah.. My Allah... Thanks to You!
Thanks to You, my Allah.
Thanks to Allah...
Your mother is alive, children.
That snake, Sofia..
...abducted your mother..
...from that cabin. -My Allah.
My brother..
My mother is alive, brother!
Brother!
My mother is alive,
brother! She is alive, brother!
My mother is alive!
Brother...
We did not lose our mother, we
still have her and her support, brother!
Thanks to Allah, brother.
Thanks to Allah. My Allah, thanks to You...
Children.
This whole struggle...
This whole struggle is to take your mother back.
But don't worry.
We will take our land back.
We will take Bala back.
We will take everything they took from us.
We will make them live through the torment of
hell while they are still alive. Don't worry.
Tell me where the tribe is. I can go myself.
You shouldn't leave Osman Bey alone.
Osman Bey gave strict orders, Meryem.
Jackals!
Meryem, run for your life!
Halime.
I promise I will find you, my daughter.
And I will make them pay..
...for the suffering they gave you.
Did you sleep well, Bala?
Sofia.
You're testing my patience.
Don't worry. There won't be another test.
We're leaving shortly.
Where is my daughter, Sofia?
You'll die before you meet your daughter, Bala.
Both you and Osman will.
You'll die today.
My Bey, we've located the temple.
We left some alps there.
They'll be watching.
There are too many soldiers, my Bey.
Both nokers(Mongolian soldiers) and Byzantine
soldiers. It's like a fortress, my Bey.
It has a strong gate.
One of us is equal to a
thousand of them, thank Allah.
Listen to me carefully.
We will split up.
One wing will attack the front side.
And the rest will get around
the back of the temple.
-Alaaddin, this duty is yours.
-As you order, my Bey.
I'll get beyond the walls with hooked
ropes and get in the back, my Bey.
Okay, okay.
Orhan!
You and alps will attack the front with me.
-Prepare the shields.
-As you order, my Bey.
My Bey, Ayaz says there is a hard gate.
We have no rams. How will we make it?
We will. We will, Aykurt.
First, we will destroy the temple.
Then, we'll save Bala.
And then, God willing, we will
take back our tribe from them.
-God willing, my Bey.
-God willing.
May your swords be sharp! Get on the horses now.
What did you do to her?
Where is my child?
You will pay for this!
It's Osman and you who will pay.
You'll be punished for everything you did to me.
And in pain
...you will beg me.
Soldiers.
Get the carriages prepared now!
Time of pain is coming.
My lady, Osman
Our watchmen have seen Osman around.
Damn it.
My Osman.
Don't have false hopes, Bala.
Osman is coming to his
death. It's fate, you know.
In the place where I raised your daughter
..I will make you two bleed...
...and hang your corpses on the temple gate!
I swear we will make you regret, Sofia.
We will never give up.
You lose, Sofia.
You lose.
Hristo, send four more soldiers to the gate.
Now we should...
...go prepare a welcome party for Osman.
We'll kill you, Sofia.
We'll kill you.
Osman's scouts.
They've already taken positions around.
This is it, my Bey.
Even the temple of those
dogs looks like a fortress.
It doesn't matter, Samil Bey. We
have faith to destroy it, thanks to Allah.
Alaaddin.
Get around in the back of the
temple with the alps. Go, son.
As you order, my Bey. Turahan.
Alps, come with me.
Orhan, are the flying flames ready?
We have enough to destroy the gate, my Bey.
Don't worry.
Okay, okay.
Come on, alps. Grab your shields.
Draw your swords.
Today is the vengeance day.
Here we go.
They'll attempt to get through the gate.
I don't want a single Turk
to get inside through it.
Reinforce it.
Place archers on the walls.
Tell them to shoot even the birds approaching!
Armored soldiers will
stand ready inside the walls.
They will be the team to slaughter Turks.
Everybody knows their duties.
-What are you doing here. Poena?
-Osman knows about the temple.
They're going to attack here.
I know.
This will be the death for Osman and Bala.
With your own eyes
...you'll witness that your
revenge has been taken.
You are the strongest woman I have ever met.
How will you do that?
Hristo.
Send a messenger to Ulugan.
The battle where Osman
and his kin are wiped out...
...will take place here.
We're under attack!
Osman's coming!
Archers!
Open!
Close!
Osman is attacking our walls, Sofia.
They're coming towards the front gate.
Let him come.
I'm the master of death.
He'll get the most
relentless response in return!
Hristo.
Osman will attempt to reach Bala.
But he will never succeed.
Build a wall of flesh in
front of Bala's door. Go!
Did you lock her in my room?
-Yes.
It's the safest place
My little bird.
Don't worry.
Today is the day when our sufferings will end.
Tell me now.
Are you ready for this holy day?
I'm ready.
Will you take revenge from those two demons?
I've been waiting for this day
for years. I'm not afraid of death.
Even if I bleed and lose my life
..I will take revenge.
Turahan.
Throw it silently.
I will go first. Follow me.
As you order, my Shahzade.
-May Allah bless our fight.
-Aameen.
In the name of Allah!
Ya Allah.
-Hang on, alps! Hang on!
-Open!
Aykurt, come on
Prepare the flying flames.
-Aykut!
-They're ready, Aykurt Cavus.
Aykurt!
Open!
Ya Allah!
Come on, warriors! Attack!
-Allah Allah! Allah Allah!
-Attack!
Fight, brothers!
Cut off their heads! Come on!
Fight for our martyrs! Fight, brothers!
Allah is the greatest!
What if Osman doesn't come?
Osman won't leave his wife alone against death.
Today both Osman and Bala are going to die.
Turks are coming!
Come here.
They can't go anywhere!
-They're coming to their death.
-Show no mercy. Kill them all!
Allah is the greatest!
Sofia, I'm here to destroy your nest.
I'll hit you in the heart. Soldiers, attack!
Orhan!
Take care of Sofia. I'm going for Bala.
Save my mother, my Bey! I got this!
Sofia.
You'll never be able to reach Bala.
Where are you going, Sofia?
First... You first should taste my sword.
Orhan, you're first that I will kill, huh?
We will see.
Come on, come on.
Come on!
This way, hurry up!
I will get out of here.
I will come for you, my Halime.
Even during your absence, you help your mother.
I promise I will find you, my daughter.
I will find you. Come on!
Come on, come on!
I will never feel sorry for you, Bala.
You deserve even worse.
Why are they so late?
Be patient.
When Osman dies.
...you will sit on the throne easily.
Besides, Osman is really going to die.
Not like Bala.
As a man existing under Ulugan's shadow,
...you are too confident, Altuga.
-Don't make a mistake and ruin things.
-Enough!
Someone's coming.
We will find out now.
Speak. Where is Sofia?
Osman attacked the temple.
I knew. He's going to save Bala.
What now?
Osman..
We'll bring their dark fate to them.
We'll present the death to them with our swords.
We're going to the temple.
I'm here, my Bala. I'm here.
Osman's coming!
Osman
Osman! I'm here, Osman!
Osman! Osman!
I am here! -Bala!
Osman! -Bala
My Bala, I found you!
Now it is time for you to die, you red demon.
I will let you come together with Lukas!
Osman is saving Bala, Sofia!
Not yet, Orhan!
Run!
We will kill you sooner or later!
Allah is Eternal!
We need to kill more of them now!
Bala!
I am here.
-Bala...
Are you alright?
-I am alright. Are you alright?
I am. Come here. Come.
Osman.
Osman, we need to find Sofia. Only
she knows where our daughter is.
Bala, what are you saying? Bala?
Do not let Sofia trick you. Bala!
Halime died.
Osman, I am telling the truth! I am telling
the truth! Sofia told me everything!
Look, she raised Halime here!
Her bed, her clothes, her smell, her comb...
Bala, we need to leave this
place as soon as possible.
We'll leave and we will
talk about it on the way.
We will face that dog if necessary. Come on.
Come on.
Look, if Halime is alive...
...don't worry...
...we will find my daughter.
Alright? -We will find her!
Come on, walk. Come on, Bala!
Come on!
Hold every place in the castle!
They will never get out of here.
Aunt!
Osman saved Bala. They are leaving.
We are losing...
We never lose, my little bird. Trust your aunt.
They will never get out of here.
We will take our revenge today.
Come on, come with me.
Catch that demon called
Sofia! Destroy that place!
We will find her brother! We will dry up
the seeds of fitna and establish peace.
-For our martyrs!
-Allah is the Greatest!
-Come on!
They are here!
You have no where to go. Drop your swords.
First, I will pierce your
hearts. Come at me! Come on!
Halime..
My Allah, keep me sane...
My Halime, is that you?
Osman, I saw my Halime!
-I saw my Halime, Osman!
Sofia is taking her away -Bala!
Bala!
Come on
Sofia!
-Bala!
-Don't take a single step, Sofia!
It's my Halime! I know!
How?
Osman. Come, look!
Look!
We found our daughter!
That is Halime standing over there.
What are you saying Bala?
Halime..
Bala is telling the truth Osman.
You found your daughter.
Bala..
Look at me..
Look at me, you red dog...
Are you telling the truth?
Even if you are telling the truth..
...or not, I will send you to hell!
Halime!
Stay where you are.
Soldiers!
You found your daughter.
But you will never be able to have her.
Before I kill you...
...tell me the truth. For the last time.
For the last time.
The truth?
The truth is standing before you.
Before I..
...send you to death...
...I will do one last favor.
The last face you see...
...will be your daughter...
..Halime's.
Halime.
You..
Is she...
Osman, it's her...
How is this possible?